We wish you a Merry Christmas,\nWe wish you a Merry Christmas,\nWe wish you a Merry Christmas\n
And a Happy New year!
Good tidings we bring to you and your kin.
We wish you a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year!
Oh bring us some figgy pudding,\nOh bring us some figgy pudding,\nOh bring us some figgy pudding\n
And bring it right here!
Good tidings we bring to you and your kin.
We wish you a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year!
We won’t go until we get some,\nWe won’t go until we get some,\nWe won’t go until we get some\n
So bring it right here!
Good tidings we bring to you and your kin;
We wish you a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year!
We all like our figgy pudding,\nWe all like our figgy pudding,\nWe all like our figgy pudding\n
With all its good cheer!
Good tidings we bring to you and your kin.
We wish you a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year!
We wish you a Merry Christmas,\nWe wish you a Merry Christmas,\nWe wish you a Merry Christmas
And a Happy New Year!